

Anastasiia Kovalenko

e-mail: koanvl88@gmail.com

phone: +34 607-39-12-18 (telegram, WhatsApp, Viber)

location: Gijon city, Asturias, Spain

portfolio website: https://koanvl.github.io/portfolio_vanka/

ABOUT ME

Hi there! My name is Anastasiia and I'm a Frontend Developer with over 5 years of commercial experience. I have experience in creating fully responsive and cross browser compatible websites, landing pages using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript/jQuery, installing and customization WordPress Themes.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Responsive Design
- React JS

- Git
- WordPress
- e-mail templates
- Photoshop/Figma
- Q&A manual
- Data analysis

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian: native

English: B2 (certificate)

Spanish: A1/A2

EDUCATION

THE NATIONAL ACADEMY OF STATISTICS, ACCOUNTING AND AUDITING

September 2005 – December 2010 Master of Economics Cybernetic Studied from September 2005 to December 2010 at The National Academy of Statistics, Accounting and Auditing. Received a Master's degree in the field of Economic Cybernetics

WORK HISTORY

BLACK CAT TECHNOLOGY

Kyiv, Ukraine August 2019 – February 2022 Front-end Developer Part time

- Created and maintained front-end code for 10+ websites from scratch (landing pages, enterprise websites)
- Working with the WordPress templates.
 Installation and design according to the customer style, filling content
- Independent creation of adaptive landing pages and websites based on WP templates without the participation of designers
- Yii and WordPress templates customization
- Q/A Manual
- Development of mathematical models of business processes requiring automation for both customers and company

ZIBOX TECHNOLOGY

Kyiv, Ukraine June 2017 – February 2019 Front-end Developer Full time

- Created and maintained front-end code for 20+ websites from scratch (landing pages, enterprise websites)
- Creation of additional modules for existing projects (price calculators, questionnaires, briffs)
- Working with the WordPress templates.
 Installation and design according to the customer style, filling content
- Working in a team with designers and back-end developers
- Recommending solutions for a streamlined, userfriendly interface with the design team
- Designing and implementing HTML email templates and newsletters for marketing campaigns
- Yii and WordPress templates customization
- Q/A Manual
- Participation in Brainstorms
- Development of mathematical models of business processes requiring automation for both customers and company

SOFT SKILLS

Team player

I have experience in teamwork. I am a faststudying person, always looking for a new knowledge and trends in my field. Always ready to shear my knowledge with colleagues. I have a mentoring experience.

People Management

I have experience managing people and establishing business processes between company departments

Time Management

I know how to plan and organize my work flow, evaluate the priority of tasks. I have a high level of self-organization and have experience working remotely with the team made in different time zones and locations.

Critical thinking

I have critical thinking and system thinking. I always decomposing tasks. Can see not only technical side of the tasks but also business side of them. (The all picture understanding)

